question_data = [
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Film",
     "question": "Brandon Routh plays the titular character in the movie &quot;John Wick&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Film",
     "question": "Han Solo&#039;s co-pilot and best friend, &quot;Chewbacca&quot;, is an Ewok.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Film",
     "question": "Samuel L. Jackson had the words, &#039;Bad Motherf*cker&#039; in-scripted on his lightsaber during the filming of Star Wars.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Film",
     "question": "Actor Tommy Chong served prison time.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Film",
     "question": "Matt Damon played an astronaut stranded on an extraterrestrial planet in both of the movies Interstellar and The Martian.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Film",
     "question": "&quot;Minions&quot; was released on the June 10th, 2015.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Film",
                                      "question": "Leonardo DiCaprio won an Oscar for Best Actor in 2004&#039;s &quot;The Aviator&quot;.",
                                      "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Film",
     "question": "&quot;Foodfight!&quot; earned less than $80,000 at box office.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Film",
                                       "question": "George Lucas directed the entire original Star Wars trilogy.",
                                       "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Film",
     "question": "Shaquille O&#039;Neal appeared in the 1997 film &quot;Space Jam&quot;.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Film",
                                      "question": "In the original script of &quot;The Matrix&quot;, the machines used humans as additional computing power instead of batteries.",
                                      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Film",
     "question": "In Alfred Hitchcock&#039;s film &#039;Psycho&#039; it is said he used chocolate syrup to simulate the blood in the famous shower scene from ",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Film",
     "question": "The movie &quot;The Nightmare before Christmas&quot; was all done with physical objects.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Film",
     "question": "In the original Star Wars trilogy, David Prowse was the actor who physically portrayed Darth Vader.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Film",
     "question": "The 2010 film &quot;The Social Network&quot; is a biographical drama film about MySpace founder Tom Anderson.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]
